<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JimmyRespawn – App</title>
    <link>https://app.linjimi.com/tags/app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in App on JimmyRespawn</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://app.linjimi.com/tags/app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Calendar Terms of Service (Terms)</title>
      <link>https://app.linjimi.com/private/168073112032/tumblr_p8dzs3gOIk1unlq99/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://app.linjimi.com/private/168073112032/tumblr_p8dzs3gOIk1unlq99/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Last updated: May 21, 2018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please read these Terms of Service(“Terms”, “Terms of Service”) carefully
before using the Game Calendar app (the “Service”) operated by JimmyRespawn
(“us”, “we”, or “our”).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of
and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and
others who access or use the Service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If
you disagree with any part of the terms then you may not access the Service.
This Terms and Usage agreement for Game Calendar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links To Other Web Sites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Service may contain links to third-party web sites or services that
are not owned or controlled by Game Calendar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game Calendar has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the
content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or
services. You further acknowledge and agree that Game Calendar shall not be
responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or
alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such
content, goods or services available on or through any such web sites or
services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy
policies of any third-party web sites or services that you visit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Termination&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may terminate or suspend access to our Service immediately, without
prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including without
limitation if you breach the Terms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All provisions of the Terms which by their nature should survive
termination shall survive termination, including, without limitation, ownership
provisions, warranty disclaimers, indemnity and limitations of liability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Governing Law&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of
Washington, United States, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be
considered a waiver of those rights. If any provision of these Terms is held to
be invalid or unenforceable by a court, the remaining provisions of these Terms
will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us
regarding our Service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might
have between us regarding the Service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Changes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these
Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will try to provide at least 30
days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material
change will be determined at our sole discretion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By continuing to access or use our Service after those revisions become
effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to
the new terms, please stop using the Service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about these Terms, please &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jimmyrespawn@hotmail.com&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Calendar No Internet Connection Troubleshoot</title>
      <link>https://app.linjimi.com/private/168073112032/tumblr_o40p708tcf1unlq99/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://app.linjimi.com/private/168073112032/tumblr_o40p708tcf1unlq99/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Hi dear user,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m very sorry you encounter this problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason why you get this message may be:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You use this app too frequently in a very short time. The server might consider you as an bot and ban you from getting data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Solution: Simply restart your router or modem to get another IP address will resolve this problem. But if you are getting the same IP address the problem will remain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your ISP or country block the data source.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Solution: in this case, you have to contact your ISP( internet service provider) to unblock Giant Bomb site to enable the app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have bad internet connection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Solution: try another time when your network environment get better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked before, keep getting this error message now.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Solution: Please contact me via e-mail( you can find my mail in wpappx.com. Tell me the app no longer work. I’ll look into it see if it’s a common issue. If it is , I’ll work on new update to resolve this issue. If it isn’t, I’m sorry you’ll have to see 1-3 and try to resolve this issue by yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
